Enas awad sello

enas.awad169@gmail.com

Enas-Sello
My web stie



Work Experience

Freelancer (20201 till now)

- User Interface Designer
- Frontend Developer

AAIB front end React.js (March 2022 - August 2022)

- · User Interface Designer
- · Frontend Developer

Markting

- Admin for clothing group in Egypt and Saudi Arsbia at facbook(2021 till now)
- American Council in Mansoura for several courses (2021)

Internships

ITI/AAIB Academy Internships (March 2022 - August 2022)

• mern | mean devlopment track ,information Technology Institute (ITI), Arab African International Bank (AAIB)

Google UX Design Professional Certificate

· Google growth UX, UI Professional track (2021 - 2022)

Projects

Amazon-clone: worked on E-commerce like amazone using React & Redux and node

Github: BackEnd, FrontEnd, Demo

Movie App: worked on movie website like Netflix using React & Redux & fakeApi

Github: Repo

Admin Dashbord: worked on E-commerce Dashbord using React & Redux and node

Github: BackEnd, FrontEnd

Chat App: worked on chat app using HTML & Css & node & sokit.io

Github: Repo

Landing page: worked on Landing page using React & Sass

Github: Repo, Demo

Profile

I graduated from Al-Azher university, I've specialized in teaching and psychological health for disabilities.

I have worked as an Arabic teacher for deaf and speechless.

I have started my career in web devlopment with FWD frond-end track by the end of 2020, I have

I studied UX design process in 2021 with google and coursera " Google UX Design Professional "

and finally I joined ITI/AAIB Academy Internship (MERN Stack).

skills

Frontend Technologies

- Html 5
- · Css 3 (bootstrap, tailwind)
- javaScript
- ECMAScript
- React
- · Redux & toolkit

Back-end Technologies

- Node js
- express is
- Nest.js

Cross Platform

· React Native

Other Technologies

- MongoDB
- git&github
- · UI/UX designing tools [Figma, Adobe XD]

Education

Psychological health Dibloma

- Psychological health of disabilities (2019 2020) Kafr El-sheikh University
- Abnormal physiology (2018 2019) Mansoura University

General Diploma in Education

· Arabic teaching Diploma (2017 - 2018)

alahzer university

arabic and islamic studies for girl, Islamic Studies Department (2013-2017)

languages

Arabic : Native English : good